//creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
	{
		numb:1,
		question:"Once upon a time there _____ (live) a man called Jupiter.",
		answer:"lived",
		options:[
			"lived",
			"was lived",
			"an lived",
			"live"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:2,
		question:"She held her bag _______, even though her arm hurt________.",
		answer:"tight; badly",
		options:[
			"tightly; bad",
			"tight; bad",
			"tight; badly",
			"tightly; badly"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:3,
		question:"Dr. Lim concluded her speech _______ stressing on Buddhaâ€™s teachings of the importance of charity.",
		answer:"by",
		options:[
			"with",
			"by",
			"at",
			"in"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:4,
		question:"I will write a letter to you tentatively ________ the dates of the program.",
		answer:"indicating",
		options:[
			"indicating",
			"involving",
			"urging",
			"guiding"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:5,
		question:"To err is ____________, to forgive is divine.",
		answer:"human",
		options:[
			"humanity",
			"mankind",
			"inhumanity",
			"human"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:6,
		question:"A preposition is usually followed by a <i>noun</i>.",
		answer: "true",
		options:[
			"true",
			"false",
			"-",
			"-"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:7,
		question:"The verb <i>to think</i> is never used in continuous tenses.",
		answer: "false",
		options:[
			"true",
			"false",
			"-",
			"-"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:8,
		question:"<i>Used to doing</i> and <i>Used to do </i> mean approximately the same thing.",
		answer: "false",
		options:[
			"true",
			"false",
			"-",
			"-"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:9,
		question:"The main verb and the direct object are not normally separated.",
		answer: "true",
		options:[
			"true",
			"false",
			"-",
			"-"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:10,
		question:"Phrasal words always consist of two words.",
		answer: "false",
		options:[
			"true",
			"false",
			"-",
			"-"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:11,
		question:"Pantry:Store :: Scullery: ______.",
		answer: "Wash",
		options:[
			"Cook",
			"Kitchen",
			"Utensils",
			"Wash"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:12,
		question:"Carpenter:Saw :: Tailor: _______.",
		answer: "Needle",
		options:[
			"Measurement",
			"Needle",
			"Cloth",
			"Sewing"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:13,
		question:"Clock:Time :: Thermometer: _______.",
		answer: "Temperature",
		options:[
			"Temperature",
			"Heat",
			"Radiation",
			"Energy"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:14,
		question:"Broom: ______ :: Soap:Wash",
		answer: "Sweep",
		options:[
			"Clean",
			"Sweep",
			"Dust",
			"Floor"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:15,
		question:"Antidote: _____ :: Antiseptic:Germs",
		answer: "Poison",
		options:[
			"Allergy",
			"Wound",
			"Poison",
			"Infection"
		]
	},
];